hive.co 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Hive.co

### HIVE PRIVACY POLICY

TicketLabs Inc. operating as Hive ( **"we" /"us"/"Hive"**) makes the website, [_www.hive.co_](https://www.hive.co/) (the **"Website"** ) available to Brands (such as merchants, media companies, artists, and more) and a brands audience ( **"Audience" /"Audience Member"/"You"""**) as a platform for engagement and content sharing, as further described in our Terms of Service located at _www.hive.co/tos_ (collectively the **"Services"** ). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, store, use and distribute information about audience members through the Services including individuals who register and create an account on Hive and individuals who access the public features of the Website and Services as visitors.

### Overview:

**This document contains important terms about Hive’s collection, use and sharing of your data and it should be read in its entirety. For ease of reference we have summarized some of the key points that you should note:**

  * **Data Collection.** Hive collects certain information when you interact with the Services either through the Website or via third party sites such as Facebook if you have chosen to connect via Facebook or other social networks or interact with curated content from Brands on third party sites that leads back to the Website. We collect personal information from you that you provide as well as information which is automatically collected through the use of cookies, web beacons and other web technologies.
  * **Data Access.** Some of the information we collect is shared with third parties including with Brands whose content you have liked or Brands who we think you might like, advertisers and service providers. Third party services (e.g., Facebook), advertisers, and advertising service providers may also collect certain information about you in connection with your use of the Services.
  * **Content Usage.** Your downloads, streaming and other content consumption through the Services ( **"Usage Data"** ) is tracked and shared with Brands for their own analysis and is used by Hive to improve the Services.
  * **Advertisements.** You may be served with targeted advertising on the Services and other platforms owned or controlled by third parties based on information about you collected both on and off the Services, including advertisements based on your location and/or Usage Data.

### Consent:

**By using the Services you consent to the use of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.** Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, your Personal Information will not be used for any other purpose without your consent. We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties with which we have business relations, including, without limitation, Brands and their representatives, venues and/or promotion companies and carefully selected organizations that want to inform you of products or services that may be of interest to you. You may withdraw your consent to the processing and/or disclosure of your Personal Information at anytime by contacting us (see further below in the section entitled: _Contact Us_ ). However, withdrawing consent may result in your inability to continue using the Website and/or the Services.

### Collection of Information:

We aim to collect, use and disclose only such information as is required to enable us to manage your account, to provide the Services, to maintain our customer/visitor lists, to respond to your inquiries or provide feedback, for identification and authentication purposes, for service improvement, to administer contests and to process payments. We will maintain the confidentiality of any contact information you provide to us on signing up for our Services or contacting us with questions and we will use it only for the purposes for which we have collected it (subject to the exclusions and disclosures we have listed in this Privacy Policy), unless you agree that we may disclose it to other third parties.

Two types of information may be collected through the Website and our Services: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. This Privacy Policy does not extend to the collection, use or disclosure of the following information which is currently not limited by applicable privacy laws: (a) information that is publicly available, such as names, addresses, telephone numbers and electronic address when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance; or (b) Non-Personal Information (as defined further below).

**_"Personal Information"_** is personally identifiable information, such as your name, home address, e-mail address, credit card information, birth date and gender. At the time of collection, we will identify the information being collected and the purposes for which it will be used. It is always your choice whether or not to provide Personal Information, but if you choose not to provide certain requested Personal Information you may not be able to use certain features of the Services and Website that require registration. We may collect Personal Information in respect of the Website through registration processes; social API authentications, communications with you; information downloads; service purchases; user support; contests; and surveys, or through any other interactions you make with our web tools.

**_"Non-Personal Information"_** is information of an anonymous nature, such as the domain used to access the Website, and the type and version of browser or operating system being fused by visitors to the Website. Included is aggregate information, which is information such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors, what pages users access or visit, and average time spent on the Website. Business contact information such as the name, title, business address, e-mail address, or telephone number of a business or professional person or an employee of an organization is not considered Personal Information.

Although the use of certain Non-Personal Information collected, used or disclosed through the Internet as described herein is not restricted (and to the extent that such is the case, the obligations under this Privacy Policy do not apply to such information), we provide information in this Privacy Policy about the collection of such information for the sake of transparency with respect to the operation of the Website. Such Non-Personal Information is collected or derived by us in the course of operating this Website. For example, our web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information that is provided through your browser or stored in a cookie when you choose to visit the Website.

### Minors:

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from persons who are under the age of 13. Any Personal Information held by us that is reasonably believed to belong to a person under the age of 13 will be deleted immediately upon such realization.

### Use of Information:

We collect information for the following purposes:

  * **Registration & Access to the Services:** We use registration information to identify you when you are logging into the Website and using the Services. In order to use member features of our Services you must provide certain Personal Information to us such as your name, address, email address, and geographic location. Your Personal Information will be disclosed to the Brands you have shown interest in through the Services and you may be contacted by them.
  * **Transactional Notifications:** We provide notifications for certain activities relating to your use of the Services such as service updates and notifications regarding your account. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.
  * **Profile Data Shared with Brands and Public Data:** Publicly available data about you that is found on third-party sites (eg. information that is publicly available on Google or Facebook) may be collected and combined with other information held about you through the Services. Brands will be able to click on your profile and have access to certain information about you if you are in their audience. This information may include but is not limited to your general location (town, city and country) your first name and data about your usage of the Services (such as your interaction with a Brand’s content).
  * **Service Delivery:** We use your personal information to respond to your queries (including requests for technical support or product information) and to deliver functionality and services requested by you. We also use your personal information to connect you with Brands you have shown interest in by downloading their songs, entering their contests, viewing their content or participating in other audience engagements. Such Brands will have the ability through the Services to update you on concerts, share other news and promotions and communicate directly with you and with audience groups you may be a member of.
  * **Marketing Communications:** If you opt-in to receive marketing communications from us, we will keep you up to date on our products and services (including events, Brands and content we think you might be interested in), upcoming surveys or contests as well as those of our affiliates and certain third parties. You may withdraw your consent to receiving marketing communications at any time by unsubscribing from certain forms of communications through your account settings, or by emailing us and requesting we do so for you.
  * **Statistics:** We also collect statistics about use of the Services through cookies and other means (see _System Logs & Cookies_ below). We collect information through the Services and Website to manage our business and perform data analyses/audits for internal use.
  * **Personalization:** We use some information collected through the Website and Services (eg. see _System Logs & Cookies_ below) to target advertising based on factors such as geographical location, gender, interests, habits, etc. and to tailor your experience on our Website and display content that we believe to be of particular interest to You (see further _Advertisements_ ).
  * **System Logs & Cookies:** Cookies are used by us to track content usage and traffic on the Website. A cookie is a feature of your web browser that consists of a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. The Website uses cookies to help it compile aggregate statistics about usage of this Website, such as how many users visit the Website, how long users spend viewing the Website, and what pages are viewed most often. This information is used to improve the content of the Website and Services. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie. This gives you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. If you disable cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of the Website. We do not link any of the information we use in cookies to any personally identifiable information submitted by you when you are on the Website. Your IP address is reported by your web browser whenever you visit a page on the Website. This information is recorded together with your registration information on our databases.
  * **Advertisements:** Advertisements appearing on the Website may be delivered by us or one or more third-party web advertisers. These third party web advertisers may set cookies. These cookies allow the advertisement server operated by that third party to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. Accordingly, advertisement servers may compile information about where or whether you viewed their advertisements and which advertisements you clicked on. This information allows web advertisers to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. The Privacy Policy applies to cookies placed on your computer by us, but does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party web advertisers. For the privacy practices of such third-party web advertisers, you should consult the applicable privacy policy for the relevant third-party web advertiser(s)

If we plan to use your Personal Information in the future for any other purposes not identified above, we will only do so after informing you by updating this Privacy Policy. See further the section of this Privacy Policy entitled _’Amendment of this Policy’_.

### Disclosures & Transfers:

We have put in place contractual and other organizational safeguards with our agents (see further below) to ensure a proper level of protection of your Personal Information (see further Security below). In addition to those measures, we will not disclose or transfer your Personal Information to third parties without your permission, except as specified in this Privacy Policy (see further _Important Exceptions_ below).

As at the date of this Privacy Policy, we share Personal Information about you in respect of the Website only with our service providers, our website host and certain third parties with which we have business relations. Our servers are also located in the United States and accordingly your Personal Information may be available to the United States government or its agencies under a lawful order, irrespective of the safeguards we have put in place for the protection of your Personal Information.

Our service providers may include software developers; system integrators and payment processors.

From time to time we may employ third parties to help us improve the Services. These third parties may have limited access to databases of user information solely for the purpose of helping us to improve the Services and they will be subject to contractual restrictions prohibiting them from using the information about our members for any other purpose.

### Important Exceptions:

We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your consent if we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Website members, other users of the Services, or anyone else (including the rights or property of anyone else) that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose Personal Information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by and in accordance with the law. We may also disclose your Personal Information in connection with a corporate re-organization, a merger or amalgamation with another entity, a sale of all or a substantial portion of our assets or stock, including any due diligence exercise carried out in relation to the same, provided that the information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information.

### Security:

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use commercially reasonable efforts to store and maintain your Personal Information in a secure environment. We take technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps designed to protect Personal Information that you provide to us. We have implemented procedures designed to limit the dissemination of your Personal Information to only such designated staff as are reasonably necessary to carry out the stated purposes we have communicated to you.

In certain areas, such as when you provide credit card or other payment information to us, the Website works to help protect the security of your credit card and other payment information during transmission by using industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.

You are also responsible for helping to protect the security of your Personal Information. For instance, never give out your email account information for the Services to third parties.

### Retention:

We will keep your Personal Information for as long as it remains necessary for the identified purpose or as required by law, which may extend beyond the termination of our relationship with you. We may retain certain data as necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained personal information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you request that your name be removed from our databases, it may not be possible to completely delete all your Personal Information due to technological and legal constraints.

### Access and Accuracy:

You have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you in order to verify the Personal Information we have collected in respect to you and to have a general account of our uses of that information. Upon receipt of your written request, we will provide you with a copy of your Personal Information although in certain limited circumstances, we may not be able to make all relevant information available to you such as where that information also pertains to another user. In such circumstances, we will provide reasons for the denial to you upon request. We will endeavor to deal with all requests for access and modifications in a timely manner.

We will make every reasonable effort to keep your Personal Information accurate and up-to- date, and we will provide you with mechanisms to update, correct, delete or add to your Personal Information as appropriate. As appropriate, this amended Personal Information will be transmitted to those parties to which we are permitted to disclose your information. Having accurate Personal Information about you enables us to give you the best possible service.

### Residents of the European Economic Area ("EEA"):

We generally process Personal Information in order to fulfill contracts we have with our brand customers and to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above in this Policy. Otherwise, we will obtain consent from an individual in respect of processing of Personal Information if required by law to do so.  Further, individuals located in the EEA (“ **EEA citizens** ”) have certain rights under European law (including under the General Data Protection Regulation) (collectively “ **EU Data Protection Law** ”) with respect to Personal Information, including the right to request access to, obtain, correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data. EEA citizens also have the right to make complaints to regulatory authorities in respect of our privacy practices. Individuals located in to the EEA who wish to exercise these rights or to learn more about such rights, should contact us at [_privacy@hive.co_](mailto:privacy@hive.co).

EU Data Protection Law sets out a number of different reasons for which we may collect and process your personal data in certain circumstances. Where EU Data Protection Law applies, the legal bases we rely upon include:

  * **Consent:** We can collect and process your data with your consent, where required by the EU Data Protection Law. For example, if you have given your consent to receiving marketing material from us.
  * **Contractual obligations:** We need your personal data to comply with our contractual obligations. For example, where you have provided us with your email address to receive access to our Services, we will use this information in order to effectively deliver and communicate information to you in regard to such products and services.
  * **Compliance with legal obligations:** If the law requires us to, we may need to collect and process your data for legal compliance reasons. For example, we can pass on details of people involved in fraud or other criminal activity.
  * **Legitimate interest:** We may require your data to pursue our legitimate interests or those of a third party in a way which might reasonably be expected as part of running our business and which does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests. For example, it is in our legitimate interests to (a) ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer and that we provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us, (b) to keep our Website and our Services safe and secure;(c) for measuring or understanding the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you (including individual and pseudonymous analysis and profiling); (d) to allow you to participate in interactive features of our Services (if applicable), and (e) to use marketing related information about you that we have lawfully collected.

If you are an EEA citizen, Personal Information that we process in relation to you may be transferred and stored at, a destination outside the EEA that may not be subject to equivalent data protection law (please see further **Disclosures & Transfers** above). It may also be processed by staff situated outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers.

We may transfer your personal data outside the EEA:

  * in order to host or store it;
  * in order to enable us to provide goods or services to and fulfil our contract with you or the company your work for;
  * where we are legally required to do so;
  * where it is in our legitimate interests and we have concluded these are not overridden by your rights.
  * Where your information is transferred outside the EEA, we take steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is subject to appropriate safeguards, such as where applicable relying on a recognised legal adequacy mechanism and contracts, to help ensure your rights and protections travel with your data and that your personal data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy.

If you are an EEA Citizen, you have the following additional rights under certain circumstances:

  * to be provided with a copy of your personal data held by us;
  * to request the rectification or erasure of your personal data held by us;
  * to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data (for example, while we verify or investigate your concerns about your information);
  * to object to the further processing of your personal data, including the right to object to marketing; and
  * to request that your personal data be moved to a third party.

### Amendment of this Policy:

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy in the future, we will post an appropriate notice on the home page at [_www.hive.co_](https://www.hive.co/). Any non-material change (such as clarifications) to this Privacy Policy will become effective on the date the change is posted and any material changes will become effective 30 days from their posting on the Website. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all Personal Information that we have about you. The date on which the latest update was made is indicated at the bottom of this document. We recommend that you print a copy of this Privacy Policy for your reference and revisit this policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Website signifies your acceptance of any changes.

### Contact Us:

You can help by keeping us informed of any changes such as a change of address or telephone number. If you would like to access your information, if you have any questions, comments or suggestions of if you find any errors in our information about you, please contact us at: [_privacy@hive.co_](mailto:privacy@hive.co).

**Last Updated: May 24, 2018**
